{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271821425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271821425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271838529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271838529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271847724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271847724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271849208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271849208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271878880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271878880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271892666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271892666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271893747","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271893747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271921790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271921790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549271927403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549271927403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272076030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272076030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272079680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272079680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272082379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272082379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272096640","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272096640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272097720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272097720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272106257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272106257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272108298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272108297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272116311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272116310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272117452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272117452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272127458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272127458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272133249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272133249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272134210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272134210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272142153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272142153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272172332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272172332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272179971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272179971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272181762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272181761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272191951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272191951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272193229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272193229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272202330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272202330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272204535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272204535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272217383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272217383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272237839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272237839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272247845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272247845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272257696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272257696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6a0cb00d-7808-4f1b-a7c2-c263b6be84d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272266557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272266557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272266792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272266791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272267766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272267765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272269055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272269054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272272014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272272014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272272874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272272873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272273197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272273196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272274445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272274445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272278017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272278017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272279014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272279014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272279280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272279279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272280235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272280234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272283117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272283116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272284165","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272284164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272284646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272284646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272289177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272289175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272289318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272289318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 6b36a835-0325-4843-b134-b2ee3ce9653b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272303414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272303413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mawe-mama-kufa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mawe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272312173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272312173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mawe-mama-kufa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" kufa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272320857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272320857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mawe-mama-kufa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272329031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272329031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_juma_juma-koti-naye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" juma"," userResponse":" juma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272338071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272338071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-ziko-huko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" ziko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272346892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272346892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-ziko-huko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" huko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272355757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272355757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-ziko-huko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" lima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272364300","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272364300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_pedi-duni-boma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" boma"," userResponse":" duni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272373147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272373146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_pedi-duni-boma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" boma"," userResponse":" pedi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272381865","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272381865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_pedi-duni-boma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" boma"," userResponse":" boma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272382429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272382429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" bede2bf5-1255-4eb3-8aa3-06d804d4ab13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_boma_pedi-duni-boma"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272388342","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272388342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 1398b120-a58e-4c6d-b72c-dbc706a7a74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272403807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272403806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 1398b120-a58e-4c6d-b72c-dbc706a7a74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272406466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272406465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 1398b120-a58e-4c6d-b72c-dbc706a7a74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272406578","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272406578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 1398b120-a58e-4c6d-b72c-dbc706a7a74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272422558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272422558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 0271c5d7-175e-4863-982a-6ee8f52b919d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272439563","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272439563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 0271c5d7-175e-4863-982a-6ee8f52b919d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272447648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272447648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 0271c5d7-175e-4863-982a-6ee8f52b919d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ma.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272450048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272450048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 0271c5d7-175e-4863-982a-6ee8f52b919d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272455242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272455241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 0271c5d7-175e-4863-982a-6ee8f52b919d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ma.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272466804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272466803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yatima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" YATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272470641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272470641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yatima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272472184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272472184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuzama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZAMA"," userResponse":" KUZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272475816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272475816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuzama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272477371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272477371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272481678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272481678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272483239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272483239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" selma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SELMA"," userResponse":" SELMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272488935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272488935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" selma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SELMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272490494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272490494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vyema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEMA"," userResponse":" VYEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272493108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272493108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vyema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEMA"," userResponse":" VYEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272494670","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272494669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wazima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272497676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272497676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wazima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272499229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272499228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" juma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272501721","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272501721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" juma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272503275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272503275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" inauma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAUMA"," userResponse":" INAUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272512377","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272512377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" inauma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272513937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272513937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" salama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" SALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272518425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272518424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" salama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272519976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272519976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272524757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272524757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ma.rand.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272526790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272526789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272526941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272526941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272566404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272566404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272580621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272580621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272587834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272587834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272595715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272595715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272603468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272603467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" 69bedb3d-dcb1-4c0c-93f3-fe194061c404"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.ma.rand.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" lilisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272612632","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272612631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipoona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272616004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272616004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272619137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272619137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAINA"," userResponse":" BAINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272622109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272622108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272625102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272625101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANA"," userResponse":" KANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272628069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272628068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272631132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272631131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINA"," userResponse":" SHINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272634231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272634230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272637601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272637600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuonekana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272641034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272641033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272644796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272644795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mvulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272644884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272644883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" f320d8ae-3e5c-453f-a02c-092fede23b97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.na.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272780809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272780809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272781031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272781031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272782006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272782006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272783294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272783293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272786188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272786188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272787042","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272787042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272787361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272787361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272788617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272788616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272792174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272792173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272793169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272793169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272793431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272793430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272794415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272794415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272797311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272797310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272798358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272798357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272798836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272798836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272803417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272803415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549272803534","data":{"timestamp":" 1549272803534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_121638"," gameId":" beada0e0-c439-492a-8240-9998e69262b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}